Scotland
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Scotland
2.1.1.1.26
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1242
- Scotland, 2.1.1.1.26
  - Detail of window at Melrose Abbey, Melrose, 1912 July 22; 35; 20001; 802; 5x7 (Box 1242)
  - General view of Melrose Abbey, Melrose, 1912 July 22; 36; 20002; 5x7 (Box 1242)
  - Melrose Abbey from cemetery, Melrose, 1912 July 22; 37; 20003; 5x7 (Box 1242)
  - Bruce’s heart, Melrose Abbey, Melrose, 1912 July 22; 38; 20004; 821; 5x7 (Box 1242)
  - Interior and East window of Melrose Abbey, 1912 July 22; 39; 20005; 822; 5x7 (Box 1242)
  - West end of Melrose Abbey, 1912 July 22; 40; 20006; 823; 5x7 (Box 1242)
  - Dryburgh Abbey, picaresque ruin, Dryburgh, 1912 July 22; 41; 20007; 824; 5x7 (Box 1242)
  - Arbistie corner at Dryburgh Abbey, Dryburgh, 1912 July 22; 42; 20008; 825; 5x7 (Box 1242)
  - Detail of Dryburgh Abbey, Dryburgh, 1912 July 22; 43; 20009; 826; 5x7 (Box 1242)
  - Tomb of Sir Walter Scott at Dryburgh Abbey, Dryburgh, 1912 July 22; 44; 20010; 827; 5x7 (Box 1242)
  - Sir Walter Scott’s burial place in St. Mary’s aisle, Dryburgh Abbey, 1912 July 22; 45; 20011; 828; 5x7 (Box 1242)
  - Abbotsford from the rear, Sir Walter Scott’s home, Abbotsford, 1912 July 22; 46; 20012; 829; 5x7 (Box 1242)
  - Vistae of Abbotsford Sir William Scott’s house, Abbottsford, 1912 July 22; 47; 20013; 829; 5x7 (Box 1242)
  - “Abbotsford”, home of Sir Walter Scott, from opposite bank of the Tweed, Abbotsford, 1912 July 22; 48; 20014; 5x7 (Box 1242)
  - Abbotsford, house of Sir William Scott, from opposite bank of river, Abbotsford, 1912 July 22; 49; 20015; 830; 5x7 (Box 1242)
  - Road to Edinburgh, from opposite side of Tweed River, 1912 July 22; 50; 20019; 831; 5x7 (Box 1242)
  Box 1243
- Scotland, 2.1.1.1.26
  - Looking up at Edinburgh Castle, Edinburgh, 1912 July 22; 1; 20020; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Looking up at Edinburgh Castle, Edinburgh, 1912 July 22; 2; 20021; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Edinburgh Castle through the trees, Edinburgh, 1912 July 22; 3; 20022; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Edinburgh Castle and fountain, Edinburgh, 1912 July 22; 4; 20023; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Looking up at Edinburgh Castle, Edinburgh, 1912 July 22; 5; 20024; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - University buildings from Princess Street Gardens, Edinburgh, 1912 July 22; 6; 20025; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - University buildings and art gallery, Edinburgh, 1912 July 22; 7; 20026; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - John Knox’s house, Edinburgh, 1912 July 22; 8; 20027; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Art gallery, Edinburgh, 1912 July 22; 9; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - The walk in Princess Street Gardens, Edinburgh, 1912 July 22; 10; 20029; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Walk and art gallery in Princess Street Gardens, Edinburgh, 1912 July 22; 11; 20033; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Sir William Scott Memorial and Livingston Statue at Princess Street Gardens, Edinburgh, 1912 July 22; 12; 20034; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Princess Street Gardens and William Scott Memorial, Edinburgh, 1912 July 22; 13; 20035; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - William Scott statue in William Scott memorial, Edinburgh, 1912 July 22; 14; 20036; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Princess Street Gardens on other side of art gallery, Edinburgh, 1912 July 22; 15; 20037; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - North British Hotel, Edinburgh, 1912 July 22; 16; 20038; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Princess Street looking toward Calbon Hall, Edinburgh, 1912 July 23; 17; 20040; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Holyroad Palace, Edinburgh, 1912 July 23; 18; 20041; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Soldier of the “Black Watch” at Holyroad Palace, Edinburgh, 1912 July 23; 19; 20042; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Fishwomen with Frank R. Roberson, outside Edinburgh, 1912 July 24; 20; 20044; 836; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Firth of Forth bridge, 1912 July 24; 21; 20045; 837; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Stirling Castle, Stirling, 1912 July 24; 22; 20046; 838; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - House of Fair maid of Perth, Perth, 1912 July 24; 23; 20047; 839; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Countryside scene, 1912 July 25; 24; 20050; 842; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Stream near Loch Oich, 1912 July 26; 25; 20053; 847; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Entrance to Caledian Canal, Banavie, 1912 July 26; 26; 20054; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Road along Caledonian Canal, 1912 July 26; 27; 20055; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Railway car, Banavie, 1912 July 26; 28; 20058; 851; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Canal, lock at Banavie, 1912 July 26; 29; 20059; 852; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Ruined tower along Caledonian Canal, 1912 July 26; 30; 20062; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Car on ferry, hold up, Ballachulish, 1912 July 26; 31; 20063; 855; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Car on ferry, before landing, Ballachulish, 1912 July 26; 32; 20064; 856; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Car on ferry, ready to land, Ballachulish, 1912 July 26; 33; 20065; 857; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Mountains and stream, near Glencoe, 1912 July 26; 34; 20066; 858; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Looking through mountains, Glencoe, 1912 July 26; 35; 20067; 859; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Mountains and Glen, Glencoe, 1912 July 26; 36; 20068; 860; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Crowd at ruins, Iona, 1912 July 26; 37; 20069; 861; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Ruins of church and Mr. Frank R. Roberson, Iona, 1912 July 26; 38; 20070; 862; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Ruins of church, sheep in foreground, Iona, 1912 July 26; 39; 20071; 863; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Cathedral and St. Martin’s Cross, Iona, 1912 July 26; 40; 20072; 864; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Detail of St. Martin’s Cross, Iona, 1912 July 27; 41; 20073; 865; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Arch in cathedral, Iona, 1912 July 27; 42; 20074; 866; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Crowd of nubber necker’s at Maclean’s Cross, Iona, 1912 July 27; 43; 20075; 867; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Tombs at Iona, perhaps Macbeth, Iona, 1912 July 27; 44; 20126; 868; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Distant view of church and ruins, Iona, 1912 July 27; 45; 20127; 869; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - “Grenadier” through trees, Iona, 1912 July 27; 46; 20128; 870; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Village of Iona, 1912 July 27; 47; 20129; 871; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - “Grenadier” from Iona, 1912 July 27; 48; 20130; 872; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Frank R. Roberson looking up in Fingal’s Cave, Staffa, 1912 July 27; 49; 20131; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Frank R. Roberson in Triv Y Als cave, Staffa Island, 1912 July 27; 50; 20132; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Fingal’s Cave, looking toward sea, Staffa, 1912 July 27; 51; 20133; 874; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  - Looking out of Fingal’s Cave, Staffa Island, 1912 July 27; 52; 20134; 5x7 (Box 1243)
  Box 1244
- Scotland, 2.1.1.1.26
  - Frank R. Roberson looking into Fingal’s Cave, Staff, 1912 July 27; 1; 20135; 875; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - “Grenadier” at Fingal’s Cave, Staffa, 1912 July 27; 2; 20136; 876; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Rock formation at Fingal’s Cave, Staffa, 1912 July 27; 3; 20137; 877; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Showing formation at Fingal’s Cave, Staffa, 1912 July 27; 4; 20138; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Rock formation, Staffa, 1912 July 27; 5; 20139; 879; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - “Grenadier” at Fingal’s Cave, Staffa, 1912 July 27; 6; 20140; 878; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Cliffs, Staffa, 1912 July 27; 7; 20141; 880; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Bridge and stream, 1912 July 27; 8; 20144; 883; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Bridge and stream, near Loch Lomond, 1912 July 27; 9; 20146; 883; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Loch Lomond toward Beu Lomond, 1912 July 27; 10; 20147; 885; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Loch Katrine from the Stronachlacer lauding, Loch Katrine, 1912 July 28; 11; 20151; 887; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Loch Arklet near Loch Katrine, 1912 July 28; 12; 20153; 889; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Loch Katrine, Lirver end, 1912 July 29; 13; 20154; 890; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Lower end, Loch Katrine, east end of lake, 1912 July 29; 14; 20076; 891; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Loch Katrine, lower end, near Ellen’s Isle, 1912 July 29; 15; 20077; 892; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Road in Trossachs, 1912 July 29; 16; 20078; 893; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Beu venue from the Trossachs Hotel, 1912 July 29; 17; 20079; 894; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Brieg of Turk, Trossachs, near Loch Achray, 1912 July 29; 18; 20080; 895; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Loch Vennachar, Trossach’s Scotch Lake District, 1912 July 29; 19; 20081; 896; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Road scene, Loch Lomond, 1912 July 30; 20; 20082; 897; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Road scene near Torbet Hotel, Loch Lomond, 1912 July 30; 21; 20083; 898; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Road scene, Loch Lomond, 1912 July 30; 22; 20084; 899; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Road scene, near Loch Lomond, 1912 July 30; 23; 20085; 900; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Road near Loch Lomond, 1912 July 30; 24; 20086; 901; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - House and trees near Loch Lomond, 1912 July 29; 25; 20088; 904; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Road view, Loch Lomond, 1912 July 30; 26; 20089; 905; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - City Hall and George Square, Glasgow, 1912 July 30; 27; 20090; 906; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - City Hall, vertical view, Glasgow, 1912 July 30; 28; 20092; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Hat store, Glasgow, 1912 July 30; 29; 20093; 4-907; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Street scene, Glasgow, 1912 July 30; 30; 20094; 907; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Street scene, shopping district, Glasgow, 1912 July 30; 31; 20095; 2-907; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Store windows, Glasgow, 1912 July 27; 32; 20096; 5-907; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Front of university building, Glasgow, 1912 July 30; 33; 20097; 9-907; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Street scene, retail stores, Glasgow, 1912 July 31; 34; 20098; 3-907; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Tiva bridge of Ayr, 1912 July 31; 35; 20101; 908; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Burns statue, Ayr, 1912 July 31; 36; 20102; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Home of Robert Burns showing garden and sun dial, Alloway, near Ayr, 1912 July 31; 37; 20103; 911; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Auld Alloway Kirk, near Ayr, 1912 July 31; 38; 20106; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Frank R. Roberson at Brig O’Doon, Alloway, near Ayr, 1912 July 31; 39; 20109; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Begonias bed at foot of Burns memorial, 1912 July 31; 40; 20110; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Herbaceous planting about Burns Memorial, Alloway, near Ayr, 1912 July 31; 41; 20111; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - General view of Burns Memorial from Brig O’Doon, Alloway, near Ayr, 1912 July 31; 42; 20113; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Fam O’Shaufer and the Sand Lord Souber, Johnny, Burns Memorial, Alloway, near Ayr, 1912 July 31; 43; 20114; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Brig O’Doon Bridge as seen from foot of Burns Memorial, Alloway, near Ayr, 1912 July 31; 44; 20115; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Brig O’Doon from Burns Memorial, Alloway, near Ayr, 1912 July 31; 45; 20116; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Looking up stream to Brig O’Doon, Alloway, near Ayr, 1912 July 31; 46; 20117; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Looking up stream from Brig O’Doon Bridge, Alloway, Ayr, 1912 July 31; 47; 20118; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Brig O’Doon Bridge, Alloway, near Ayr, 1912 July 31; 48; 20119; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Brig O’Doon Bridge, close-up, Alloway, near Ayr, 1912 July 31; 49; 20120; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Hayfields, near Ayr, 1912 July 31; 50; 20121; 10-908; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Landscape planting around Burns Memorial and monument, Alloway, near Ayr, 1912 July 31; 51; 20122; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Border of annuals, Burns Memorial, Alloway, near Ayr, 1912 July 31; 52; 20123; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  - Burns Memorial, Alloway, near Ayr, 1912 July 31; 53; 20124; 5x7 (Box 1244)
  Box 1245
- Scotland, 2.1.1.1.26
  - Front view of Burns Cottage, Alloway, Near Ayr, 1912 July 31; 1; 20125; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Loch Lush, reflections in water, 1912; 2; 20049; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Loch Lush near Fort Augustus, 1912; 3; 20048; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Bridge over stream, Fort Augustus and Fort Williams, 1912 July; 4; 20057; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Roslyn church, Roslyn, 1912; 5; 5x7 (Box 1245)